[{"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": 1}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": 1}, "sum": 2, "item": 1}}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}, {"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": 1}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": 2}, "sum": 3, "item": 1}}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}, {"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": 1}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": 3}, "sum": 4, "item": 1}}], "answers": [3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}, {"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": 1}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": 4}, "sum": 5, "item": 1}}], "answers": [4], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}, {"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": 2}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": 1}, "sum": 3, "item": 2}}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}, {"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "num": 2}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "num": 2}, "sum": 4, "item": 2}}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}, {"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": 2}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": 3}, "sum": 5, "item": 2}}], "answers": [3], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}, {"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": 3}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": 1}, "sum": 4, "item": 3}}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}, {"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "num": 3}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "num": 2}, "sum": 5, "item": 3}}], "answers": [2], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}, {"body": [{"type": "look-picture-fill", "title": "填一填", "stem": "看图填数", "splitObj": {"left": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": 4}, "right": {"img": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": 1}, "sum": 5, "item": 4}}], "answers": [1], "resource": "", "explain": "", "knowledges": ["5以内数的合与分"], "level": "1", "type": "填空", "number": "1-1-7-01"}]